
### v9-onN7EsWo 167
0: Hello, I am Kim Jeong-ah, a nurse practitioner working at Eminent Hospice Care.
1: Today, I will talk about one of the most frequently asked questions when starting
2: hospice care.
3: If you go to hospice, will you recover quickly?
4: I will give you the answer to this question, or a similar question:
5: will you start using morphine right away if you go to hospice? People who ask this
6: Yes, the bottom line is that this is not the case.
7: Hospice is the cause and the patient is not going to pass away anytime soon.
8: According to research on hospice,
9: There are statistics showing that hospice recipients live longer when they receive
10: hospice services than when they do not receive hospice services.
11: Because we have seen the process many times,
12: we are able to take unnecessary samples and respond quickly according to the
13: disease the patient has and the symptoms that come with it. So the family can
14: When receiving hospice services rather than caring for the patient alone,
15: the patient is able to better manage their current symptoms,
16: making the patient more comfortable.
17: The patient also wants to live longer,
18: and the likelihood of actually living longer increases.
19: Managing medications well at a hospice also contributes to the amount and quality
20: of the patient's life.
21: It contributes a lot to improving quality.
22: One of the misconceptions about hospice is that some people think that if they do
23: hospice, they will stop taking all their medications. In conclusion,
24: that is not the case.
25: Hospice is not about giving medicine,
26: but organizing it and often leaving medicine that is really necessary and helpful
27: to the patient. As time goes by,
28: There are cases where the drug becomes more of a burden to the patient than the
29: expected effect of the drug. The most common cases are dementia drugs.
30: Dementia drugs are used to treat dementia.
31: There are drugs that prevent the progression of dementia rather than drugs that
32: treat it. If dementia has already progressed to the terminal stage,
33: it is not about seeing the expected effect,
34: but about the patient's current condition.
35: There are times when it is recommended to stop taking the medicine because it may
36: have a worse effect on the patient's condition. In other cases,
37: continuing to take the medicine may affect the patient's condition.
38: Depending on the condition, there are cases where it can actually be harmful.
39: If the patient is maintaining a normal condition, it is not a big problem,
40: but if the patient's condition worsens,
41: In case of blood pressure, diabetes, cholesterol, you need to be careful.
42: We often say that we need to take diabetes, blood pressure,
43: and cholesterol medications until we die.
44: This is a word that emphasizes the need to continue eating without stopping,
45: but it only applies when the patient maintains a normal condition.
46: Those who actually come in as hospice patients.
47: There are many people who come in because they can't eat,
48: but when you control blood pressure and diabetes,
49: there are often people who already have low blood pressure and low blood sugar.
50: Their family members can't eat.
51: I think it's because I feel a sense of responsibility that I must take medicine
52: even if I do it. If I don't eat well,
53: I will lose weight and my blood pressure and sugar will drop.
54: The possibility increases. If you continue to take blood pressure or diabetes
55: medications in that condition, low blood pressure and hypoglycemia may occur,
56: which can cause death. In the case of cholesterol drugs,
57: It is a medicine that removes cholesterol from the body,
58: but if you explain to your family that there is no need to remove fat that has
59: already been stored when you cannot eat, they will help you.
60: The cases described so far where you understand and agree to stop are general in
61: nature. Blood pressure varies depending on the patient.
62: There are some people whose sugar levels rise unexpectedly,
63: so the family checks the patient's blood pressure, amount of food, and swallowing.
64: You should carefully monitor your overall condition and consult with a medical
65: professional to decide when to stop taking the medication.
66: A nurse will visit regularly.
67: Depending on the patient's disease and symptoms,
68: we discuss with the family what to monitor and how to make the patient more
69: comfortable.
70: If the patient consults with the doctor about whether the medicine will be helpful
71: or not and takes the adjusted medicine,
72: the patient will feel comfortable and his or her condition will become more stable
73: than before.
74: We often see cases like this, so it can be said that it is a misunderstanding to
75: say that if you use hospice, you will die quickly.
76: I would like to tell you about pin.
77: There are people who use morphine in extreme cases.
78: There are many cases where people have a reaction. Of course,
79: it is a drug that must be used with extreme caution.
80: Starting hospice does not necessarily mean starting morphine.
81: No. You can think of two reasons for starting morphine:
82: those who have difficulty breathing and those who have pain.
83: Dyspnea is a difficulty in breathing that occurs before death.
84: You may have difficulty breathing in the terminal stage,
85: and the page you originally had can be an example of difficulty breathing in the
86: terminal stage. If you have difficulty breathing during the interim period,
87: use morphine.
88: Even if it is not a pre-existing condition,
89: an example is difficulty in breathing in the stage of lung disease.
90: In cases of difficulty in breathing in the end stage of lung disease,
91: morphine is often used.
92: I told you that other cases of using blood are when the pain is severe.
93: Cancer pain is also the worst among narcotic analgesics.
94: We may start with a mild one and give you morphine at the end.
95: And if your symptoms are severe and you cannot take it by mouth,
96: we may give you morphine that you can put under your tongue.
97: Let's start. You can think of the pin that can be placed under the tongue as a
98: fast-absorbing morphine that is absorbed into the blood vessels under the tongue
99: in very small amounts.
100: In conclusion, the reason for using morphine is to relieve breathing difficulties
101: and pain, thereby making the dying process shorter and more comfortable.
102: The purpose is that we always ask for the family's consent when starting morphine
103: because it can accelerate the death of a person while in bankruptcy in Korea.
104: In many cases, there are people who ask to start morphine late because their
105: family lives out of state or someone who lives in Korea has to come to watch the
106: deathbed.
107: We discuss with the family and adjust the starting time.
108: And many Koreans think of morphine as an injection.
109: People are praying. Most hospices in the U.S.
110: give the water blood potion drive before death. Drop it with brown rice.
111: However, start with a very small amount using a small syringe or dropper.
112: Approximately 5mg 0.5c, 0.25cc.
113: Let me start by telling you about the effects of morphine. In my experience,
114: there are many people who tried morphine and found it had no effect.
115: About half of them did.
116: I think if there is no effect,
117: you can increase the dose slower or more frequently.
118: And you can think that you have seen the desired effect for the remaining half of
119: the time.
120: It seems that the desired effect is to alleviate shortness of breath and reduce
121: pain. There are also some people who see unwanted effects. Very few.
122: This is a case. There are people who lose consciousness due to an allergic
123: reaction, mental impairment, fusion, or complete loss of consciousness.
124: That's why we tell our family members before starting morphine. Lastly,
125: there is someone who saw results that exceeded expectations, and in this case,
126: To put it simply, morphine suits the patient very well.
127: Symptoms improve more than expected. As an extreme example,
128: I gave him morphine because I thought he would return.
129: This is a case where the patient's mind and mood improve because the body becomes
130: so relaxed and comfortable after taking the pin. So,
131: the patient lives a little longer.
132: There are people who live comfortably. So far,
133: I have talked about the effects of morphine.
134: Morphine is not used in all patients. Morphine is not used in all patients.
135: There are people who die. People who die while sleeping do not use morphine.
136: Also, breathing slows down.
137: There are some people whose breathing is very shallow.
138: They rest gently or slowly and start breathing if there is no pain.
139: No. Lastly, I would like to end by talking about the importance of medication
140: management. If you are not a nurse attending to patients,
141: or if you are taking care of elderly people,
142: Children and caregivers will know all too well,
143: but many Korean seniors are really bad at managing their medications.
144: The names of the medications are written in zero.
145: Therefore, there are cases where patients or their families are not familiar with
146: the name of the medicine and do not know why they are taking the medicine,
147: so they take it as they please.
148: There are many problems. There are many overlapping medications.
149: The doctor said I should stop, but I didn't stop,
150: and I am taking two at the same time.
151: You may be eating it, or you may have stopped but it would be a waste to throw it
152: away, so you may be storing it up and then forgetting to eat it again later.
153: Or, because the medicines are like that,
154: there are too many medicines and you are confused as to which medicine you should
155: take and which medicine you should not take.
156: Pharmacies continue to provide refills,
157: but because patients take their medications sparingly,
158: there are cases where they end up taking too many medications.
159: The people who see this are a bit younger.
160: I tell you this because I am a generation.
161: There are so many good medicines in the world.
162: Medicines can save people or make them die quickly. I have many such medicines.
163: I get so many cases. Please tell me to be smart about medicine,
164: what medicine I take, what effect it has, and when to take it.
165: Please keep in mind what you should and should not do and manage your medication.
166: That’s it.

### XeGjlf7fILA 130
0: Hello, I am Kim Jeong-ah, a nurse practitioner who works at Eminent Hospice Care.
1: Today, I am talking to people who are asking about what happens to the patient's
2: family after the patient passes away.
3: This happens often. So, let me explain what procedures are followed in the United
4: States when a patient passes away.
5: Depending on whether you were in hospice or not at the time and where you were,
6: the procedures you need to follow after you pass away are different.
7: Let me explain. First, I will explain the case where a patient dies while in
8: hospice care. Hospice care means that the doctor has already decided that the
9: patient will die.
10: This means that the patient applied for hospice in anticipation of this,
11: and the family agreed to allow the patient to die at the current location.
12: So, hospice
13: No matter where the patient dies,
14: the patient can immediately call the hospice office. Then,
15: the hospice staff will go out and declare death.
16: The nurse leaves, and after declaring death,
17: the hospice office calls the funeral company and makes arrangements to take the
18: patient there.
19: I give it to you. Sometimes, there are family members who ask to take the deceased
20: to the hospital after 2 hours or so. In most cases,
21: the family does not spend time with the patient.
22: So, you may want to spend more time with the deceased,
23: or the bereaved family is coming from far away,
24: so you are asking for that waiting time,
25: but the hospice office is not able to accommodate the time for the family.
26: However, California law requires that the patient be moved from the current
27: location of death within 4 hours after death.
28: Since this is the law, most of the time,
29: I take the deceased to the disability association.
30: Let me talk about something else for a moment. Sometimes,
31: Among the family members of patients in the United States,
32: there are those who believe that they must call 911 when the patient dies.
33: In many cases, if a patient dies without hospice care,
34: it is correct to call 911. However, if the patient dies while in hospice care,
35: You don't have to call Nine 1 Won, you can just switch to Spieth Office.
36: It is usually operated by Koreans.
37: If you are a funeral home, it will take less than two hours.
38: If you are an American funeral home, you can think of it as taking up to four
39: hours. Then, depending on where you passed away.
40: Let me tell you another thing. This is a case where the patient is recognized by a
41: nursing hospital. Since there are already mutual aid nurses at the nursing
42: hospital, those nurses are the ones who declare the death.
43: After declaring death, the hospice company is called.
44: The spisa company calls the funeral home chosen by the family in advance.
45: And if the patient admits it at the Yangno Hotel or at home,
46: the medical staff will go there to pick up the patient.
47: Since there is no one, if you call the hospice office,
48: a hospice staff member will leave. I told you that a nurse will usually leave,
49: but that nurse is
50: When you declare death and call the hospice office,
51: the hospice office also calls the funeral home pre-determined by the family and
52: takes care of the patient, that is, the deceased.
53: We will make arrangements so that the deceased can be taken out. Then,
54: after taking the deceased to the funeral,
55: the funeral director will inform the hospice office of a death wash.
56: This Death Watch contains information to be included in the death certificate.
57: For example, the patient's information and
58: Enter the information of the doctor who will write the death certificate,
59: time of death, and cause of death, and send it to the funeral home by fax or
60: email.
61: The funeral director then reports the death to the state with that information,
62: and the state sends something called a physical station to the hospice office.
63: funeral home is where the doctor finally confirms the death of the patient.
64: Then, this physical station is performed.
65: The station is sent to Stay, and once all verification is completed,
66: Stay sends the death certificate certificate to the funeral home.
67: Only when all cutting documents are completed can the funeral company proceed with
68: the funeral ceremony for the patient, cremate the patient,
69: or place the patient in the cemetery.
70: In summary, the place where you first start playing Death War is Jangsa,
71: and the place where the Sammang medical certificate finally arrives is also
72: Jangsa.
73: If the person died during the week,
74: the death certificate can be completed within 2 or 3 days.
75: If the person died on the weekend,
76: the death certificate can be completed within 2 or 3 days after the weekend.
77: If the funeral company is late or the doctor is late in confirming the cause of
78: death, the death certificate may be delayed.
79: The family can call the funeral home after the funeral company takes the
80: deceased and discuss disability procedures.
81: After the death certificate is completed at the funeral,
82: you can request as many death certificates as necessary from the funeral home.
83: Lastly, in hospice, a spiritual counselor calls the patient's family after the
84: patient's death to offer words of comfort. The spiritual counselor
85: You can mainly think of it as a hospice chaplain.
86: Spiritual counselor service can be thought of as a spiritual stone in Korean.
87: Spiritual care is also provided.
88: It is one of the core services that must be provided by a hospice.
89: Spiritual care service is defined by Medicare as a service that must be provided
90: by a hospice.
91: It means that the hospice service period is just as a nurse visits regularly to
92: take care of the patient's physical symptoms.
93: A pastor visits the patient and takes care of his/her spiritual needs.
94: A chaplain at the end of life provides comfort to the family.
95: After delivering my speech, I will talk about Lehman Reel services. In fact,
96: it is a bit unfamiliar to Korean sentiment, but if I were to translate it:
97: This is a bereaved family letter service.
98: This is a service in which a hospice sends a letter of consolation to the bereaved
99: family for a certain period of approximately one year.
100: The contents of the letter are:
101: It may be different for each hospice company, but in our company's case,
102: we provide a checklist of things to check after death to help family members or
103: bereaved families who have lost someone close to them overcome the depression or
104: sadness they may experience.
105: Methods Expected changes in life during the mourning period include poems of
106: comfort, etc. Lastly, I would like to briefly talk about what it means to do
107: hospice.
108: Hospice is gradually becoming more known to Koreans,
109: but it is still considered an uncomfortable word to hear.
110: There is an internist I used to know and the patient is.
111: When he complained that he was in a lot of pain due to arthritis,
112: he said this: Arthritis is a disease that only occurs with age,
113: but it is possible to develop arthritis.
114: Living to old age is truly a blessing.
115: I don't know how many people have passed away before even getting arthritis.
116: As you know, these days, there are so many incidents.
117: There are too many accidents and even young people are struck by diseases such as
118: cancer or rare diseases, so there are too many people who die before they get
119: older.
120: In a sense, it can be said that it is natural to welcome people who are older and
121: more prepared. It is sad to let go of someone leaving their family,
122: but it can be avoided.
123: It is impossible. Hospice is a service that helps you spend the last journey of
124: your life in a more meaningful and comfortable way.
125: If you have any questions, please contact us at any time.
126: Please. Today, I explained the procedures for dying patients when a patient dies
127: during hospice care. Next time, the patient will receive hospice care and
128: I will tell you what end-of-life procedures you will go through when you pass away
129: and what post-death procedures you will go through. Thank you.

### SNGsCjicC8E 131
0: Hello, I am Kim Jeong-ah, a nurse practitioner who works at Eminent Hospice Care.
1: In the last video, if the patient acknowledged that he or she was receiving
2: hospice,
3: I told you about the subsequent procedures. Today,
4: I will explain the subsequent procedures if the patient admits to it without
5: receiving hospice.
6: First, it is a hospital. Patients who die at the hospital die while receiving
7: treatment, so call this funeral home after the medical staff declares death.
8: During the funeral, the deceased is taken out of the hospital.
9: The next case is when the patient dies in a nursing home.
10: In the nursing hospital, the patient's heart stops and the patient is not
11: breathing.
12: If this is discovered, an advance directive is important.
13: It is important to know in advance how much medical care the patient will perform
14: in a life-threatening condition.
15: This is a set document. It's called Apost ers for Raph Streamer.
16: It's a bit awkward if you say it in Korean,
17: but it's a bit awkward when you say it in Korean.
18: A doctor's order is just an advance directive in Korean.
19: It's usually a pink piece of paper that indicates whether or not to administer
20: cardiopulmonary water if the heart stops.
21: There is a case where renal failure is required when a CPR check is performed.
22: At this time, the medical staff calls 911 while performing cardiopulmonary
23: treatment.
24: You need to send them to the hospital.
25: There are cases where patients exercise a lot and if cardiopulmonary resuscitation
26: is required, check the CPR Ordinary Research.
27: In this case, the medical staff must call Nine One One while performing CPR and
28: send the person to the hospital. In cases where many Koreans are confused,
29: it is only a CPR heart massage.
30: What you are thinking about is CP,
31: which means not only cardiac massage when necessary,
32: but also regular cardiac shock and bronchial examination.
33: Carpel water and mineral water.
34: If you do not do so, you have marked the dnr double research table.
35: In this case, cardiopulmonary resuscitation is not performed and the medical
36: staff declares death and contacts the bereaved family.
37: If you call the funeral home chosen by the bereaved family,
38: the bereaved family will take you out. However, if it is not a DNR,
39: the medical staff will provide CPR bottled water as I mentioned earlier.
40: Personnel should come and do everything possible to resuscitate the patient.
41: They can take the patient to the hospital.
42: You can also declare death on the spot. When the nursing home calls me,
43: a paramedic paramedic will come, and sometimes a fire demon police will come as
44: well.
45: There are times when, in Korean, an ambulance, a fire truck,
46: or a police car come along. Since these three places are in charge of emergency
47: treatment, anyone is the best.
48: They come from the place where they can come first,
49: and the rest may arrive one after the other or may not arrive according to the
50: situation. In some cases, the police will come and ask if there is anything
51: suspicious about the death.
52: After investigating to see if there was anything wrong,
53: a funeral director can be called once the investigation is complete. However,
54: the police are suspicious of this death.
55: If we do, we will conduct further investigation and contact County Coroner.
56: County Coroner will be called by the coroner.
57: This coroner will come out and perform an autopsy on the deceased.
58: You will decide whether to take Geomchi to the location or not.
59: If you take Geomchi with you, you will have to decide again whether to conduct an
60: autopsy.
61: Then, the last case is if you die at home or in a hospice.
62: If you die outside of a hospice, you can go to a regular home or a seasoned hotel.
63: Anyone who was there should call 91. When you call 911, as I mentioned before,
64: one of the Paramedic Fire Demons or Police comes out first.
65: In general, paramedics are emergency medical staff.
66: Most nursing hospitals have post offices and pre-hospital facilities,
67: but homes and nursing homes have them.
68: Since there are very few people present and there is no one who can make an
69: official declaration of death, we have to call 911.
70: So 911 comes and checks to see if there is a DNR or not, and if not,
71: perform a possible failed resuscitation and try to prolong life.
72: All measures must be taken. Nevertheless, if he dies,
73: he must declare death and ask the police whether death is natural.
74: This is a suspicious person. First of all,
75: the family is already in shock due to the sudden death and will wait until the
76: investigation is completed.
77: Because the police do not allow them to touch or move the deceased,
78: the bereaved family goes through an even more mentally difficult situation.
79: So, especially those at home,
80: Hospice treatment is sometimes recommended to avoid the complicated process that
81: must be experienced after death. If a patient dies without hospice treatment,
82: In general, your attending physician will assist you with the necessary procedures
83: for writing a death certificate. Now, this time,
84: I would like to tell you more about funeral directors.
85: The company mainly has patients in Orange County, LA,
86: so people living in Geumgum, LA should use a Korean funeral home.
87: It is often used. When a patient dies, a funeral home takes them there,
88: and afterwards a funeral ceremony is held. At the funeral,
89: guests are invited and the entire funeral ceremony is held.
90: After finishing, you will be moved to a burial or cremation location.
91: In general, funeral companies run by Koreans are easy to talk to and have the same
92: culture, so they will take care of it.
93: Koreans prefer Korean disability companies because they handle everything in the
94: Korean style. Some American funeral directors are cheap and some are expensive.
95: It's up to you.
96: Rather than giving it to you, there are many options and Koreans often feel
97: uncomfortable due to different cultures.
98: Even though the price may be a bit expensive,
99: people tend to prefer Korean companies that communicate well and have common
100: culture. Among foreign funeral directors, funeral directors tend to
101: There is a company that provides funeral services in places where there is a
102: cemetery. So when you pass away, you can provide funeral services and take your
103: person to the graveyard without having to go right away.
104: Because of this, the price is a bit expensive.
105: Disability costs vary depending on the funeral home,
106: and the more you decide in advance, the more you can compare prices,
107: services, etc. and choose.
108: Therefore, it is advisable to prepare in advance as much as possible.
109: Also, applying cremation is another case. This is also a case where a cremation provider
110: run by a Korean and a foreigner are used.
111: There is a cremation provider that operates, but there is a bit of a price difference.
112: One thing I would like to tell you is that unless you are financially struggling,
113: Regardless of the price, those who do not want to invite a lot of people and want
114: to do cremation frugally and simply with someone they know at a low price usually
115: choose foreign companies.
116: It can also be used. So far,
117: I have told you about Lim Jong-woo's general procedures.
118: Before ending the video, I would like to briefly talk about your attitude toward
119: death.
120: In Korean culture, people are very reluctant to talk about death because they
121: think that everything is over when they die, and they often think of it as a sin.
122: On the other hand, Western culture seems to think of death as just another natural
123: journey of life. I really have seen a lot of deaths.
124: I saw that dying well seems to be the end to living well. Because I lived well,
125: I think I can die well. I can see the person who is dying.
126: I become humble every time, and I promise to live a meaningful life until I go
127: before God in this one-time life.
128: I hope it will be helpful to those who watched the video. In the next video,
129: if you do hospice,
130: You're coming back. I'll be back with this question. Thank you for watching.
